http://www.csis.org/privacy-policy

Trade and International Business
Energy and SustainabilityEnergy, Climate Change, and Environmental Impacts
Energy and Geopolitics
Energy Innovation
Energy Markets, Trends, and Outlooks
Global HealthFamily Planning, Maternal and Child Health, and Immunizations
Privacy Policy
We do collect identifiable information about you through this site as required to register for events or email. We have access to such information only if you choose to share with us either directly, by e-mail or by filling out and submitting any information that may be available on the site. We do not and will not sell information about users of the site to third parties. Nor do we share such information except as described below.
In certain instances, we may contract with nonaffiliated companies to perform services for us. Where necessary, we will disclose information we have about you to these third parties. In all such cases, we provide the third party with only the information necessary to carry out its assigned responsibilities and only for that purpose. And we require these third parties to treat your private information with the same degree of confidentiality that we do. In addition, we will release information about you if you direct us to do so, if we are compelled by law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances. If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this privacy policy, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes.
CSIS tracks IP addresses (the Internet address of a computer) to keep track of a user's session. Tracking IP addresses can give us important information about our visitors. For example, we can learn which parts of the site users are visiting and how long they stay. When CSIS receives information about you or about your session, we may use it for research or to improve the site and the services we offer you.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us webmaster@csis.org.
